Search for:  

[Home](https://isrii.org/) » Privacy Policy
-------------------------------------------

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Notice**  
The International Society for Research on Internet Interventions (ISRII) is committed to protecting the privacy of all members and guests who visit the ISRII website. This policy was developed in the interest of protecting that privacy. This policy applies only to ISRII’s website, www.isrii.org. It does not apply to the websites of any member or liaison organization. It does not apply to any websites operated by organizations or groups who associate themselves with ISRII, nor does it apply to any websites featuring links to the ISRII website. Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of organizations or persons not owned, controlled, managed or employed by ISRII. This policy will be periodically reexamined as technology, business and legal requirements change. 

**Collection of Information**  
When you browse ISRII’s website as a guest, you are anonymous. ISRII does not collect personal information about any person that is not provided voluntarily. We track anonymous information, such as which pages were visited and for how long, on our server. We use this information solely to learn more about trends on the website, such as which web pages users visit most and how quickly information is found.

If you apply for membership, register for an event or request any other product or service, ISRII collects information from you such as your name, title, company, address, phone, fax and email address. This information is collected only if you give it voluntarily. Information provided to ISRII will be used internally in order to process your specific request and will not be sold or shared with outside parties. Your information may be used to send you ISRII publications, information relating to upcoming ISRII activities or important membership announcements. In addition, ISRII makes members’ contact information available to other members through the members-only portion of the website. This information can only be accessed with a legitimate ISRII username and password; for this reason, we strongly urge you limit unauthorized access to your ISRII username and password. You may edit your contact information at any time through the members-only portion of the website or by calling or emailing ISRII Headquarters at +1 720.724.7744 or info@isrii.org.

**Disclosure of Information**  
ISRII may occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as bulk mailing or publication printing. We provide those companies only with the information they need to complete to service they have been contracted to perform, and they are prohibited from using the information provided for any other purpose.

ISRII may disclose your information if we are required to do so by law or if such disclosure is necessary to: comply with a legal order; defend ISRII or its employees, affiliates or partners; or protect the personal safety of ISRII employees, affiliates, partners, members or site users.

**Credit Card Information**  
You may choose to provide ISRII with credit card information to pay for membership dues, event fees or any other product or service. We will never voluntarily disclose your credit card information to any third-party organization or person who is not employed by ISRII to process your payment.  
_We urge members and all other end users not to send credit card information via e-mail, instant messaging or social media, because these methods are not secure and could cause the data to be compromised.  
_

**Cookies**  
Cookies are commonly used by websites in order to make accessing that website faster and more efficient. Many organizations use cookies to track your shopping cart, for example, so that you can purchase several items or services at one time instead of having to purchase each item at the time you select it. ISRII uses cookies to monitor statistics regarding your visit to the website (such as how long you visited, what web pages you visited on our site, etc.) and to hold items in your shopping cart for you. We use “session-only” cookies, which are deleted from your computer’s memory when you close your browser window. You can set your internet browser to not accept cookies, or to ask you before accepting certain types of cookies, but this may keep you from having access to all of the benefits of the ISRII website. Using cookies in this manner is standard across the majority of all websites.

**Security**  
ISRII has taken measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information on this website. We have the technology in place to provide a secure server for transmission of data to and from our website. All information (including your address and credit card information) is encrypted when sent through our secure server so that no other party can access it.

**Disclaimers:**

* Any material published on the ISRII website is protected by International Intellectual Property and Copyright laws. All text, logos, graphics, icons, photographs, software and audiovisual material fall under this protection. Permission is granted to download, copy or print material on ISRII’s website for personal, instructional or non-commercial use only.
* The information found on the ISRII website should not be used as medical, legal, business or tax advice.
* Our Privacy Policy may be revised occasionally. You should review it from time to time to be sure you understand the details. Using the ISRII website indicates your agreement to the policy that is posted at the time of use.

### Links

### Resources

[Directions for the International Society for Research on Internet Interventions (ISRII)](http://www.jmir.org/2006/3/e23/)

### Contact Us

6728 Old McLean Village Dr

McLean, VA 22101 USA

### Connect With Us

Copyright © 2023 — International Society for Research on Internet Interventions (ISRII)

X

RETURNING MEMBERS: To access the new portal and the members-only section of the ISRII Website, please reset your password by clicking "having trouble logging in?" on [this page](https://isrii.app.neoncrm.com/login)
